{
    "subject": "resource/Imad_Abu_Zahra",
    "predicate": "http://purl.org/linguistics/gold/hypernym",
    "object": "resource/Journalist",
    "human_readable": "Imad Abu Zahra is a Journalist.",
    "questions": [
        {
            "score": 0.916159987449646,
            "question": "Is Imad Abu Zahra a writer?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.8369390368461609,
            "question": "Is Imad Abu Zahra involved in media?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.8067638874053955,
            "question": "What is Imad Abu Zahra's occupation?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.7295703291893005,
            "question": "What is Imad Abu Zahra known for?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.7108900547027588,
            "question": "What is Imad Abu Zahra's profession?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.5830316543579102,
            "question": "Does Imad Abu Zahra report on news?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.49528053402900696,
            "question": "What field is Imad Abu Zahra involved in?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.39496085047721863,
            "question": "What type of work does Imad Abu Zahra do?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.3521798849105835,
            "question": "What does Imad Abu Zahra do for a living?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.326318621635437,
            "question": "What industry does Imad Abu Zahra work in?"
        }
    ],
    "google_pages": [
        {
            "url": "https://www.google.com/search?q=Imad Abu Zahra is a Journalist.",
            "html": "dbpedia_2005_0.html"
        },
        {
            "url": "https://www.google.com/search?q=What does Imad Abu Zahra do for a living?",
            "html": "dbpedia_2005_1.html"
        },
        {
            "url": "https://www.google.com/search?q=What type of work does Imad Abu Zahra do?",
            "html": "dbpedia_2005_2.html"
        },
        {
            "url": "https://www.google.com/search?q=What field is Imad Abu Zahra involved in?",
            "html": "dbpedia_2005_3.html"
        }
    ],
    "selected_docs": [
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_2005_14.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_2005_31.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_2005_38.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_2005_50.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_2005_53.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_2005_55.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_2005_56.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_2005_60.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_2005_66.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_2005_82.txt"
        }
    ],
    "final_question": "Is true?",
    "responses": {
        "gemma2": {
            "short_ans": 1,
            "full_ans": "```json\n{'output': 'yes'}\n``` \n"
        },
        "llama3.1": {
            "short_ans": 1,
            "full_ans": "Here is the evaluation of the triple \"Imad Abu Zahra is a Journalist\" based on the context information:\n\n{\n  \"output\": \"yes\"\n}\n\nThe documents consistently describe Imad Abu Zahra as a \"freelance journalist\", a \"journalist and photographer\", or simply a \"journalist\", which supports the triple."
        },
        "qwen2.5": {
            "short_ans": 1,
            "full_ans": "```json\n{\n  \"output\": \"yes\"\n}\n```\n\nThe documents clearly state that Imad Abu Zahra was a freelance journalist and photographer, confirming the statement that he is a journalist."
        },
        "mistral": {
            "short_ans": 1,
            "full_ans": " {\n    \"output\": \"yes\"\n   }"
        }
    },
    "need_tiebreaker": false,
    "tiebreakers_responses": {
        "qwen2.5:14b": {},
        "llama3.1:70b": {}
    },
    "final_decision": 1,
    "actual_decision": 1,
    "analysis": {
        "stratum": "The Least Popular",
        "topic": "-"
    },
    "errors": {}
}